{"title": "Rescueland!", "listOfQuestions": [{"question": "What is the primary material used for the indestructible fighter ships?", "correctAnswer": "Darkmaterial", "wrongAnswers": ["Eleha", "Force Field Gel", "Techanda"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the main purpose of the Energy Scoop in Rescueland?", "correctAnswer": "Transforming energy with 100% efficiency", "wrongAnswers": ["Create food energy", "Power weapons", "Run androids"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What kind of gas injected into Rescueland robots gives them personality?", "correctAnswer": "Rescueland Gas", "wrongAnswers": ["Oxygen", "Force Field Gel", "Eleha Dioxide"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What technology allows atmospheric vehicles to transition into outer space?", "correctAnswer": "Atmospheric Bubble", "wrongAnswers": ["Energy Scoop", "Teleporter", "Force Field Gel"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which type of weapon is described as capable of turning enemy fire into usable power?", "correctAnswer": "Energy Absorption Shields", "wrongAnswers": ["Plasma Shields", "Hydro-Bombs", "Sonic Blasters"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which planet is the capital to the Seperatists?", "correctAnswer": "Recola", "wrongAnswers": ["Klesone", "Computerland", "Helucky"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the function of the Verdant Shield Projector?", "correctAnswer": "Temporary protection of Rescueland", "wrongAnswers": ["A primary ship shield", "Repairing damaged ships", "Teleporting to other planets"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which of the following is a variant of Force Field Gel with destructive capabilities?", "correctAnswer": "Mutant FFG", "wrongAnswers": ["Destructive Force Fields", "Monster Force Field Gel", "Magnetic Force Fields"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which Rescueland robot type the most modern?", "correctAnswer": "FCRT's", "wrongAnswers": ["FRJ's", "UF's", "Hulk Super FRJ's"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is Rescueland's primary defense technology called?", "correctAnswer": "Force Field Gel", "wrongAnswers": ["Plasma Shields", "Energy Shields", "Magnetic Fields"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which Rescueland material is specifically designed to absorb energy attacks?", "correctAnswer": "Energy Absorption Shields", "wrongAnswers": ["Force Field Gel", "Plasma Shields", "Teleporter"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What kind of material is Pakira known for?", "correctAnswer": "Affordability and malleability", "wrongAnswers": ["Indestructibility", "Resistance to water", "Resistance to fire"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What role do Regular FCRT's primarily serve?", "correctAnswer": "Civilians and soldiers", "wrongAnswers": ["Pilots", "Spies", "Instructors"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which engine colour represents the cleanest engine technology?", "correctAnswer": "White", "wrongAnswers": ["Green", "Red", "Yellow"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which explosive weapon is capable of annihilating a small army?", "correctAnswer": "Hydro-Bombs", "wrongAnswers": ["Rockets", "Slit Bombs", "Cannons"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What material is known for its striking blue sheen and durability?", "correctAnswer": "Krython", "wrongAnswers": ["Eleha", "Conductium", "Quorite"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which objects do the Super Owls wear?", "correctAnswer": "The Rings", "wrongAnswers": ["The Bracelets", "The Necklaces", "The Watches"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which type of laser beams are known for their abilities to stun, destroy, and apply telekinesis?", "correctAnswer": "Beamers", "wrongAnswers": ["Basic Lasers", "Hyperion Fusion Cannons", "Solar Beam Projectors"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the primary function of the Teleporter?", "correctAnswer": "Instantaneous jumps between space and dimensions", "wrongAnswers": ["Time travel", "Space expansion", "Teleporting into FFG's"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What robot is known for being disguised as an asteroid?", "correctAnswer": "Spy FCRT's", "wrongAnswers": ["Pilot FCRT's", "Regular FCRT's", "UF's"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What technology is utilized to knock out devices?", "correctAnswer": "Electromagnetic Pulse", "wrongAnswers": ["Energy Shields", "Force Field Gel", "Teleporter"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who typically leads the Rescueland army during military conflicts?", "correctAnswer": "Commander of War Weda", "wrongAnswers": ["Alpha Commander", "General Nox", "Emperor Kepson"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the weapon capable of harnessing the power of a star?", "correctAnswer": "Solar Beam Projectors", "wrongAnswers": ["Hyperion Fusion Cannons", "Conductium Cannons", "Plasma Cannons"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which cannon type is the most widely utilized?", "correctAnswer": "Universal Cannon", "wrongAnswers": ["Small Cannon", "Extra Small Cannon", "Large Cannon"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "How often do Rescueland robots require replenishing the Rescueland Gas?", "correctAnswer": "Every hundred years", "wrongAnswers": ["Every year", "Every decade", "Every millennium"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What type of aliens are the inhabitants of Rescueland primarily?", "correctAnswer": "Robots with personalities", "wrongAnswers": ["The Greys", "Rescuelandians", "Avian"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the primary purpose of the Anti-Bunker Drill?", "correctAnswer": "Penetrate bunkers", "wrongAnswers": ["Destroy enemy ships", "Launch surprise attacks", "Halve enemy troops"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What kind of technology does the AquaPurifier provide?", "correctAnswer": "Clean drinking water", "wrongAnswers": ["Electricity", "Nutritional supplements", "Weapons manufacturing"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who governs the Helucky faction?", "correctAnswer": "The Great Computer", "wrongAnswers": ["High King", "The Council of Elders", "Emperor Tarvos"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is Quorite known for in terms of durability?", "correctAnswer": "Resistance to wear and tear", "wrongAnswers": ["Resistance to fire", "Resistance to water", "Resistance to air"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What does the LightSphere device offer?", "correctAnswer": "Customizable lighting solutions", "wrongAnswers": ["Control of a star", "Air purification", "Water filtration"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What does the Exoskeleton Suit mainly enhance?", "correctAnswer": "Strength and mobility", "wrongAnswers": ["Speed and agility", "Intelligence and creativity", "Defensive capabilities"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the general atmosphere composition of Rescueland?", "correctAnswer": "Nitrogen 90%, Hydrogen 8%, Oxygen 1%", "wrongAnswers": ["Oxygen 55%, Argon 30%, Nitrogen 15%", "Hydrogen 50%, Nitrogen 40%, Oxygen 10%", "Argon 80%, Oxygen 20%"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "How often does (regular) FFG need to be taken down?", "correctAnswer": "Every ten years", "wrongAnswers": ["Every five years", "Every twenty years", "Once a year"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which type of ship is the bulk of the Helucky army made of?", "correctAnswer": "Interceptors", "wrongAnswers": ["Fighter ships", "Cargo ships", "Battle ships"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What protective feature does FCRT DarkArmour offer?", "correctAnswer": "A thick defensive layer that is nearly impossible to penetrate", "wrongAnswers": ["Provides invisibility", "Increases speed", "Allows teleportation"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which following laser is known for its ability to latch onto targets?", "correctAnswer": "P-series Laser", "wrongAnswers": ["Beamers", "Hyperion Fusion Cannons", "Solar Beam Projectors"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What materials are commonly integrated into the designs of slit bombs?", "correctAnswer": "Techanda and Eleha", "wrongAnswers": ["Pakira and Solita", "Darkmaterial and Krython", "Quorite and Conductium"], "timeout": 15}], "time given": "15"}